(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-12T22:34:07.731609",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
※公演開始までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will begin shortly. Please wait a moment.
ご来場のお客様へ：照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援 OK です
To Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is OK.
For Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights / Cheering loudly is ok.
PENLIGHT COLORS
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration Open Now!
ローソンにお越しのみなさん
Hello to everyone visiting Lawson!
ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
[Lawson Campaign Confirmed!]
今回はこの6人が登場！
[These six members will appear this time!]
詳細は3/9(月)公開予定！
[Details scheduled to be released on Monday, March 9th!]
今年のバンダイブースも熱い！
This year's Bandai booth is also hot!
注目の新商品を初公開！
First public reveal of featured new products!
会場限定、スペシャルフォトブース！
Venue-exclusive special photo booth!
ブースで限定カードがもらえる！
Get exclusive cards at the booth!
最新プロジェクトも公開！
The latest project will also be revealed!
待ってるよ！
We're waiting for you!
hololive 5th fes. Capture the Moment
hololive 6th fes. Color Rise Harmony
今年も
This year as well...
hololive STAGE 1, 2, 3, 4
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams JOYSOUND みるハコで配信決定！
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams streaming on JOYSOUND Miruhako!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here.
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say thank you again and again,
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's get on board!
ridin' on dreams
yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! hey!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream,
想像できないような
into something unimaginable,
想いになったんだ
it became a strong feeling.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が船になる
our bonds will become our ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety,
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
we can just blow it away!
果てない旅路を今
On this endless journey now,
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
there will surely be difficulties along the way.
それも力に変えて
Turn even those into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ！
and let's move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it won't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's cross over the rough seas.
「らしく」輝いていたい
I want to shine "like myself".
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, meeting you,
ねえ、宝物だから
hey, is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world with no map,
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep on going!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey!! (hey!!) hey!! (hey!!)
yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
A sudden wind
行く先乱そうとも
might mess up our path,
あの日誓ったんだ
but we made a promise that day,
覚悟は揺るがない
our determination will never waver.
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
Thinking "I have to do this right!",
明日への橋になる
it becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We have to cherish it more,
「あたりまえ」は無いから
because nothing is "taken for granted".
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story that starts from a tiny boat,
どっから始めたらいいか もがいて
struggling with where we should begin,
少しずつね 輪になって見つけた
gradually forming a circle and finding
何にも代えられない夢だ
a dream that cannot be replaced by anything.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Loving even our incomplete selves,
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
our feelings are as one.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even with a glimmer of hope,
僕と君でずっと
you and I will always
馬鹿にされても
even if they make fun of us,
信じたい！
want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" is not enough.
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing.
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were here.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it won't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's cross over the rough seas.
「らしく」輝いていたい
I want to shine "like myself".
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, meeting you,
ねえ、宝物だから
hey, is my greatest treasure.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The performance will begin shortly. Please wait a moment.
ご来場のお客様へ：演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援 OK です
To All Visitors: Please be aware of flashing lights. Vocal cheering is allowed.
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration is now open!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, thank you so many times...
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ 乗り込もう！
Now, let's climb aboard!
Ridin' on Dreams
Yeah!
Wow oh oh...
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Yeah!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a tiny dream...
想像できないような
into something unimaginable...
想いになったんだ
my feelings have grown.
わくわく止まらない！
The excitement just won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が船になる
our bond will become our ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety,
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
we can blow it all away!
果てない旅路を今
Now, on this endless journey,
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
there will surely be difficulties as we row.
それも力に変え
Turning even those into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ！
let's move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough seas together.
「らしく」輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you...
ねえ、宝物だから
is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map...
まだまだ行こう！
let's keep going!
Ridin' on Dreams
Wow oh oh...
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Yeah!
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden wind
行く先乱そうとも
tries to disrupt our course,
あの日誓ったんだ
we made a promise that day.
覚悟は揺るがない
Our resolve will never waver!
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
The pressure to "do things right"...
明日への橋になる
will become a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね<
We have to cherish it even more,
「あたりまえ」は無いから
because nothing can be taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small ship,
どっから始めたらいいか もがいて
struggling with where we should even begin.
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
Bit by bit, forming a circle, we found...
何にも代えられない夢だ
this irreplaceable dream.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Loving even our imperfections,
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
our thoughts are as one.
Wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even if it's just a tiny hope,
僕と君でずっと
you and I will always...
馬鹿にされても 信じたい！
believe in it, even if they mock us!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" isn't enough.
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing.
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough seas together.
「らしく」輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you...
ねえ、宝物だから
is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an uncharted world with no map...
まだまだ行けるから！
Because we can still keep going!
ひとりじゃない
You are not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
No matter how many times, let's stand back up,
笑い合っていたい
and keep laughing together.
願いだってみんなで、さあ！
Let's take our wishes together, come on!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Holding hands, exceeding even our imagination!
フブミオは夫婦
[Sign: FubuMio is a married couple]
Vの天使にしてくれてありがとう！ YAGOO
[Sign: Thank you for making me a V-Angel! - YAGOO]
ねねち愛してる
[Sign: Nenechi, I love you!]
エリート巫女 さくらみこ
[Flag: Elite Shrine Maiden Sakura Miko]
あじあじ
[Screen: Aji-aji]
ホロメンが好きだ！！
[Screen: I love the Holo-members!!]
ホロリスも好きだ！！
[Screen: I love the Holo-listeners too!!]
フブちゃん痛車で来た!! from 高知
[Sign: I came in a Fubu-chan itasha!! from Kochi]
Ouro Kronii on a Jetpack
[Sign: Ouro Kronii on a Jetpack]
魂の応援
[Tablet: Soul's Support]
ときのそら
Tokino Sora
さくらみこ
Sakura Miko
大空スバル
Oozora Subaru
大神ミオ
Ookami Mio
桃鈴ねね
Momosuzu Nene
獅白ぼたん
Shishiro Botan
ラプラス・ダークネス
La+ Darknesss
アイラニ・イオフィフティーン
Airani Iofifteen
クレイジー・オリー
Kureiji Ollie
小鳥遊キアラ
Takanashi Kiara
エリザベス・ローズ・ブラッドフレイム
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
ジジー・ムリン
Gigi Murin
セシリア・イマーグリーン
Cecilia Immergreen
ラオーラ・パンテーラ
Raora Panthera
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉 届け
May the harmony of our overlapping words reach you!
たどたどしく描いては
Tracing it out clumsily...
ぎこちないと笑ってた
...we laughed at how awkward it was.
未来予想 あの日の続きを見よう
Let's look at the future we envisioned, and see what lies ahead.
手と手繋いで
Hand in hand,
風も着こなして
riding the wind,
波音叩いて
beating along with the waves...
連れて行くよ
...I will take you with me!
どんなこともきっと 一緒なら叶えていける
No matter what happens, if we are together, we can surely make it come true.
らららら
La-la-la-la...
鳴り止まない希望の音 ほら
Listen, the sound of hope never stops ringing!
らららら
La-la-la-la...
聞こえてる 聞こえてる 歌おう
Do you hear it? Yes, we hear it! Let's sing!
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Our harmony, these overlapping words...
鮮やかな日々の向こう
...beyond these brilliant days...
ずっと君と 君と
...always with you, with you...
広がっていくストーリー
...this story continues to unfold.
ハーモニー 結んだ夢が
Our harmony, the dream we forged together...
宇宙へ 駆けていく
...soars toward the sky.
煌めきに乗せて あなたへ
Carried on this sparkle, straight to you,
届け メロディ どこまでも
reach out, melody, to the ends of the earth!
何気ないことも愛おしく
Even the casual everyday moments are so precious...
思い出す
...to look back on.
きゅんと痛いけど 楽しむ魔法の言葉
The magical words to enjoy even a sudden pinch of pain...
一息ついて 振り返って また君を知って その度に
Take a breath, look back, and get to know you again...
ちょっと勇気出して 明日へ飛び込んでいけ
...and every time, muster up some courage to dive into tomorrow!
La la la la... 降り積もる 道しるべは まだ
La la la la... The accumulating signposts are still...
La la la la... 覚えている？ 歌う
La la la la... Do you remember? We sing.
ハーモニー 手を伸ばしたら 足跡に虹がかかる
Harmony! If we reach out our hands, a rainbow will span our footprints.
きっと晴れる 口ずさむステージ
It'll surely clear up on this stage we hum upon.
パートナー 記した場所へ 運ぶ約束を 輝きに乗せて
Partner! Let's carry our promise to the marked place, riding on the shine...
世界へ 響け メロディ いつまでも
...and let the melody echo out to the world forever!
君と踏み出した あの一歩あの瞬間が 宝物だって 胸を張る今
That step we took together, that moment is a treasure I can proudly boast of now.
歩いて話して急いで競って
Walking, talking, rushing, competing...
色褪せないまま
...without ever fading away.
混ざり合う僕らの声ほら聞こえている
Look, our blending voices can be heard!
歌う
We sing...
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉 鮮やかな日々の向こう
Harmony! Beyond these brilliant days of overlapping words,
ずっと君と 彩るよストーリー
I'll always paint this story together with you.
パートナー 結んだ夢が 空へ駆けていく
Partner! Our bound dreams soar high into the sky,
きらめきに乗せて あなたへ
...riding on the sparkle, to you...
世界へ 響け メロディ
...and let the melody echo out to the world!
どこまでも
No matter how far!
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ_
Parade, Parade, Parade! It's time to take the stage!
呼び合う声を合図に
Using our calling voices as a signal...
Parade, Parade, Parade! 探してゆく
Parade, Parade, Parade! We go searching...
スタートは何度だって_
...for we can start over as many times as it takes.
ただ独り言を 綴った
I simply wrote down my monologues,
ただ 始まりたくて 走った
I simply ran because I wanted to begin.
遠く 暗がりに 灯った
Lit far away in the darkness,
それは 眩しすぎた 名前
...was a name that shone far too brightly.
それは 優しすぎる 思い出もっと
With memories that are far too kind,
近づけと手を伸ばした
...I reached out to get closer.
思いがけず結び合った
Unexpectedly, we bound together,
ほら 今 迷子は僕らになった
...and look, now those lost children became "us."
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It's time to take the stage!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring along both your regrets and your love,
風、夢、羽 飛び立ってるさ
For our wind, dreams, and wings are taking flight.
ささやかな祈りは光 終わりなき兆し
These modest prayers are our light, an endless sign.
君を見つけたこと胸を張れるよ
I can stand proud of having found you.
ここから これから Our Bright Parade, Parade!
Starting from here, starting right now, our bright parade, parade!
まだ頼りない予感を
Let's sing of this still uncertain premonition,
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
...there's absolutely nothing to be ashamed of.
誰も解けない イマジナリー
An imaginary world that no one can unravel,
いつかまた逢える おまじない
...is our charm to meet again someday.
ゼロに始まったストーリー
A story that started from zero...
数え切れない言の葉 数えるような想いじゃないさ
Countless words, it's not a feeling you can just count
ほら今 僕らを 一つと呼ぼう
Look, now, let's call ourselves "one"
Parade, Parade, Parade! 美しいんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It is beautiful!
許し合える刹那 夜はきらめく
The moments of forgiveness, the night sparkles
雨、晴れ、カレイド またとない空
Rain, shine, kaleidoscope, a sky like no other
ふさわしい旅路とは 君と在ることさ
The journey that fits us is being with you
君と在ることなんだ
It's being with you
「ただいま」を聞けば
When we hear "I'm home,"
「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
We'll shout, "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that natural?
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It shines!
暗がりを満たすのは 君だ 僕だ
What fills the darkness is you, it's me!
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It shines!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring along your regrets and your love
風、夢、羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings, we can take flight
ささやかな祈りは光 終わりなき兆し
A modest prayer is a light, an endless sign
君と飛び込んでゆく 素敵なスタートさ
Diving in with you, what a wonderful start
ここから これから Our Bright Parade, Parade!
From here, from now on, Our Bright Parade, Parade!
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
ホロライブ・サマー、開会宣言！たくさん楽しんでいくぞー！
Hololive Summer, opening declaration! Let's have a ton of fun!
ちわー！ホロライブ2期生、大空スバルでーす！
Hello! Hololive 2nd Gen, Oozora Subaru here!
みんな会いたかったぞー！スバルのソロ、始まるよー！
I missed you all so much! Subaru's solo is starting now!
いつだって愛情が先に走り出す僕らのランウェイを
Love always takes off first on our runway
感情とラッキーを盾に進みます Are you ready?
Advancing with feelings and luck as shields, are you ready?
転んだって泣いたって僕ら慣れてるよ受け身はパーフェクト
Even if we fall or cry, we're used to it, our fall technique is perfect
笑ってくれてありがとう
Thank you for smiling for me
また僕は歌えるよ
I can sing once again
人生は不安ばっか
Life is full of anxieties
正直自信はないけど
To be honest, I have no confidence, but...
君の隣だけは譲る気はないのです
I have no intention of giving up the spot right next to you
僕らが出会えた奇跡の世界
In this miraculous world where we met
君の目にどう映るかな
I wonder how it looks in your eyes
青空に渡る
Crossing over into the blue sky
僕らだけの空だといいな
I hope it's a sky just for us
確かな永遠より僕は
Rather than a guaranteed eternity,
二人で過ごす「今」を歌いたいんだ
I want to sing about the "now" we spend together
この地球（ほし）の片隅 続くアイ・マイ・ミー・マイン 永遠にダンシング
In a corner of this planet, continuing I-My-Me-Mine, dancing forever
ナンセンスな現実が心を乱していった
A nonsensical reality was throwing my heart into chaos
ラッキーの天秤の裏側にあるアンラッキー
The bad luck on the flip side of the scales of good luck
転んだって泣いたって僕ら立ち上がる七転八倒さ
Even if we fall or cry, we'll stand back up, struggling and striving
笑ってくれてありがとう
Thank you for smiling for me
まだ僕は走れるよ
I can still keep running
人生の期待感は
To be honest, expectations for life
正直膨らむばっかでさ
Are only continuing to expand
君の心の中 灯る陽だまりなのです
It's like a sunny spot glowing inside your heart
僕らが暮らしてる奇跡の時代
In this miraculous era that we live in
君のこと照らせるかな
I wonder if I can shine a light on you
星よりきらめいた僕ら
If we, who sparkled brighter than stars,
太陽になれたら
Could become the sun
確かな永遠より僕は
Rather than a guaranteed eternity,
二人で過ごす「今」を楽しんでいたい
I want to enjoy the "now" we spend together
すこやかなときも
In sickness and in health,
病めるときもきっと
...and even when ill, surely
伝えたいよ
I want to convey to you...
このメロディー
...this melody.
僕らが出会えた 奇跡の世界
The miracle world where we met,
君の目にどう映るかな
how does it reflect in your eyes?
青い鳥 すみわたる
The blue bird in the clear sky,
僕だけの特別な物語
it's a special story just for me.
確かな永遠より僕は
Rather than a certain eternity, I...
二人で過ごす今を歌いたいんだ
...want to sing of the present we spend together.
この星の片隅につづく
Continuing in a corner of this planet...
アイ マイ ミー ユエニ ユー アンド ミー
I, My, Me, therefore You and Me,
アイ ラブ ユー
I love you,
マイ マイ マインド
My, my mind!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
ステージ、楽しんでいくぞ！
Let's keep enjoying the stage!
I'm way too cool for this
I do my thing, no rules for this
I get that bag, it's lucrative
Feel furious, look closer, it's so obvious
How I can make a scene
Jump with my energy
I'll make you scream it loud, loud, loud
Serve it up, on a platter leave no crumbs
Eat it up
That's just my ego
It's your attention
To the center of the stage, I feel it
Pumping through my veins
Show me, show me, show me let's go
It's my, it's my, it's my, it's my ego, go, go
Living for your applause
I'll reign supreme either way, XO XO Ego
Fueling up my fantasy, I'm breaking through
It's just my ego, go, go
Ooh, I'm doing what they thought I couldn't do
XO XO Ego
The rise and fall
of a pop Messiah, ah
Yeah, I'm on the ego trip, my mirage is real, it ain't no trick
I don't hold my tongue, I know what it is
I'm your favorite sweet, yeah I'm that bitch
Jealous hearts say I'm conceited and they're right
Ain't no shade, either way they're gonna write
She's so explicit, but stay in my mentions
Got your attention, baby, that's your business
It's my, it's my, it's my, it's my, it's my, it's my ego, go, go
Living for your applause
I'll reign supreme either way, XO XO Ego
Fueling up my fantasy, I'm breaking through
It's just my ego, go, go
Ooh, I'm doing what they thought I couldn't do
XO XO Ego
Ego, they say I'm a show-off
Ego, XO XO Ego
Ego, don't like it? So what?
みんな一緒に！
Everyone, together!
EGO!
I can't hear you!
ラストいくよ！
One last time!
EGO!
That's just my ego
XO XO
刮目せよ！
Pay close attention!
今日のフェスも盛り上がっていくぞ！
Let's heat up today's festival too!
現地の皆も、ネットで見てる皆も、たくさん楽しんでってね！
Everyone here at the venue, and everyone watching online, have a blast!
いくぞ！
Here we go!
目眩もそう 深紅 みたいな
Dizziness, just like deep crimson...
カラフル 染まれ ノスタルジー
...colorfully dyed in nostalgia.
奪い去ってよ もっと狂わせて
Snatch me away, drive me even crazier.
揺れるアダムとイブ 暇を持て余してる
A swaying Adam and Eve, wasting away their free time.
私 また 昨日と同じ
Once again, just like yesterday...
形して 黙ってる
...I remain silent in the same shape.
ねぇ 寒くて 前に進めないの
Hey, it's too cold to move forward.
それくらい 察してよ
At least realize that much.
哀しい 終わり方
What a sad way to end.
ばかり話 考えたがってる
...only wanting to talk and think.
ま、それでいいわ。今日も美味しいと愛らしい振りをして
Well, that's fine. Pretending to be lovely, saying "It's delicious!" today as well.
壁に染み付いた、君が呼吸をした跡が
On the wall is the stained trace of where you breathed...
この部屋に漂った
...floating around this room,
酸素を腐らせて
...rotting the oxygen...
私を死にたらしめる
...to bring me to my death.
でもさ、もし終止符みたいにさ
But, you know, if like a period...
改札口まで伸びのび伸びる
...stretching all the way to the ticket gate,
そんな幸福も めでたいか
...do you want to cherish that kind of happiness?
揺れながら暇を持て余している
Swaying back and forth, with too much time on my hands.
しかし、また昨日と同じ
But once again, it's the same as yesterday.
轍に抜けなくなっている
Stuck in the rut, unable to break free.
ねえ、だるくて体が動かないの
Hey, I'm so lethargic my body won't move.
今日くらいは優しくして
At least be gentle with me today.
寂しい言葉を垂れ流し
Spilling lonely words everywhere,
晒しばったり合っている
...exposing them and running into each other.
まあ、それで済めば世話は無いと
Well, if that was all it took, there'd be no trouble.
加湿して夢を冷ませて
Humidifying, let my dreams cool down.
君の好きな色になりたいの
I want to become your favorite color,
いつか消えてしまうように
...so that I might disappear someday.
出口を塞いだら
If the exit is blocked,
終わらない夜が訪れる
...an endless night will come.
苛立たしさ、真実見えないが
Anxiety, though the truth is invisible,
桃源郷、息と化します
...utopia turns into a mere breath.
マリーマリー、そう拙い努力足りないが
Mary, Mary, my poor efforts aren't enough,
今はただお留守番だてら
...but for now, just while keeping watch...
揺れている
...I am swaying.
イェーイ！みんな手拍子して！
Yeah! Everyone, clap your hands!
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hey! Hey! Hey!
見えてるよー！ありがとうー！
I can see you! Thank you!
長い長い夜を彷徨って
Wandering through the long, long night,
笑い方も忘れてしまった
...I've even forgotten how to laugh.
悲劇のストーリーが
A tragic story...
私の心を狂わせる
...drives my heart mad.
でもさ、もし終止符みたいにさ
But, you know, if like a period...
改札口まで伸びのび伸びる
...stretching all the way to the ticket gate,
そんな幸福も めでたいか
...do you want to cherish that kind of happiness?
揺れながら暇を持て余している
Swaying back and forth, with too much time on my hands.
苛立たしさ、真実見えないが
Anxiety, though the truth is invisible,
桃源郷、息と化します
...utopia turns into a mere breath.
マリーマリー、そう拙い努力足りないが
Mary, Mary, my poor efforts aren't enough,
今はただお留守番だてら、揺れている
...but for now, just while keeping watch, I am swaying.
あぁ、はぁ～
Ah, ha~
ラ、ラ、ラ、ラ...
La, la, la, la...
ありがとう！
Thank you!
噛んだ！また噛んだ！
I stumbled! I stumbled!
まだまだいくぞー！
We're still going!
エリザベス・ローズ・ブラッドフレイム
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
ジジ・ムリン
Gigi Murin
セシリア・イマーグリーン
Cecilia Immergreen
ラオーラ・パンテーラ
Raora Panthera
Don't, don't know me, unpredictable
I'll rise, I'll rise
and then you die!
Standing on the edge, don't call me unpredictable, typical you
Got nowhere to go, show you something real
My level, though you'll never know, I'm a boss, so
Everything you need to know
みんなー！盛り上がってるー！？
Everyone! Are you hyped up?!
Run in the light, almighty oh
What's wrong, what's right...
Basking in the fantasy
Wanna be deceased
Sure that you will never make it out
Ice cold, but now, do it, do it, do it
Me, target like them now, now
Enemy, got us down, oh
We are guilty, hard to rule
We are not gonna stop, it's just us
Storm!
What do I like? What do I like?
Get down! Get down! Down! Down! Down!
Let's go!
Bring out the devil below
Did you already know?
Don't shy, let's go with it
Run in the light, almighty oh
What's wrong, what's right with you
Run in the night, almighty oh
Cope with, cope with, another ending in the...
Storm!
Just like that, that, that!
Justice! Justice! Justice!
We rise!
We rise! Yeah!
Standing on the edge, don't call me unpredictable, typical you
Got nowhere to go
Show you something real
My level, though you'll never know, I'm a boss, so
Everything you need to know
Standing on the edge, don't call me unpredictable, typical
Got nowhere to go
Look at them, look at them, look at them, look at them, baby
My level, though you'll never know, I'm a boss, so
It goes below
まずは、じゃあ、自己紹介しようか！
First, let's introduce ourselves!
そうだね！
That's right!
おー！
Yeah!
みんな、こんそらー！
Everyone, Kon-Sora!
元気？
Are you well?
ときのそらです！
I'm Tokino Sora!
はーい！
Okay!
ホロライブ5期生、いや、カバー株式会社、あ、ホロライブプロダクション、ホロライブ所属
Hololive 5th Generation, no, Cover Corporation... ah, Hololive Production, Hololive affiliate...
オレンジ色担当5期生、ねぽらぼのね、みんなの心の...
In charge of orange, 5th Gen, Nepolabo's Ne, of everyone's heart...
最高峰！桃鈴ねねです！よろしく！
...the peak! Momosuzu Nene! Nice to meet you!
おお、すごい熱気！
Wow, so much energy!
ね、すごい熱気！
Right? So much energy!
ていうか、ねねとぬんのペア、珍しくない？
By the way, isn't the Nene and Nun pair rare?
本当に珍しいよね！
It really is rare, isn't it!
あっ、最前に猫いるじゃん！猫いるじゃん！
Ah, there's a cat in the front! There's a cat!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
あっ、そらともさんも見えてるよー！
Ah, I can see Soratomo-san too!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
今日は、なんと、なんと...
Today is, surprisingly, surprisingly...
なんと！
Surprisingly!
2日目！
The second day!
そうだね、昨日からだから、2日目だー！
That's right, since yesterday, it's the second day!
え、昨日から連日来てるよーって人！
Who here has been coming consecutive days since yesterday?
おお、めっちゃいる！めっちゃいる！
Wow, there are so many! So many!
かなりいる！すごい！
Quite a lot! Amazing!
いつも来てくれてありがとうございます、本当に！
Thank you so much for always coming, seriously!
今日、初めて来た人ー！
Who here is visiting for the first time today?
あ、いっぱいいる！
Ah, there are so many!
本当にみんな、嘘ついてない？
Is everyone really telling the truth?
まあ、昨日から来てる気分の人もいるかもしれないしね。
Well, some might feel like they've been here since yesterday.
あ、そうだよね！そうだよね！
Ah, that's right! That's right!
気分大事、大事！
The feeling is important, important!
というわけでね、今回の4th Fesのテーマは「Our Bright Parade」ということでね。
And so, the theme of this 4th Fes is \"Our Bright Parade\".
なんか、みんなと架け橋の形がね、あったじゃん？
Like, there was a bridge of connection with everyone, right?
トロッコっていうやつが！
That thing called the trolley!
トロッコすごかったね！ / すごかったね！
Nene: The trolley was amazing! / Sora: It was amazing!
みんなの近くに行ったよ！見たかな？
We went close to everyone! Did you see us?
見たかなー？
Did you see us?
えー、じゃあ今日のハッシュタグについて、ちょっとおさらいしていきたいと思います！
Okay, so let's quickly review today's hashtag!
ハッシュタグは、ホロ...
The hashtag is, holo...
フェス エキスポ！
Fes Expo!
えー、2024、
Uh, 2024,
カバー、Day 2です！皆さん、たくさんポストしてください！
Cover Day 2! Everyone, please post a lot!
してください！
Please do!
確かに。じゃあ、何々？
True. So, what should we do?
ちょっと聞いてみようかな。
I think I'll ask them.
お、何聞くの？
Oh, what are you going to ask?
日本のみんなー！
Everyone in Japan!
海外のアニキ！
Overseas brothers!
おー、すごい！
Wow, amazing!
すごーい！色んなところから来てくれてるよ。
Amazing! People came from all over.
ありがとう！嬉しいね。
Thank you! We're so happy.
違う違う、みんなとしゃべる時間だから！
No, no, this is our time to talk to everyone!
こんなにたくさんの人の前で、スケベができることなんて中々ないから。
It's not often we get to do naughty things in front of so many people.
そういう意味だったの？！違う違う！
That's what you meant?! No, no!
全然気づかなかった！
I didn't realize at all!
タッチさせてよ。タッチさせてよ。
Let me touch you. Let me touch you.
何を？
What?
触っていい？
Can I touch you?
あ！ああ、もう、ぽぽぽぽ...
Ah! Ah, geez...
最高な気分だ、みんな！
I feel great, everyone!
みんなも楽しんでるか？！
Are you all having fun too?!
せっかくさ、私たちがさ、MC1番目じゃん？
Since we are the first MC segment, you know?
うん、最初のMC任されちゃった！
Yeah, we were entrusted with the first MC!
そうだよ。だからもう、みんながやりそうなこと全部やっちゃおう！コーレスとか、ウェーブとか！
So let's do everything everyone else would do! Like call-and-response, or waves!
やっちゃおう、やっちゃおう！
Let's do it, let's do it!
ねぇねぇ、コーレスで、ぬんにぴったりのやつ考えたから。
Hey, I thought of a call-and-response that's perfect for Nun.
何かある？
Is there one?
ぬんは今日も？って聞いたら、みんなが「ぬんぬん！」って返す。
When Nun asks "Nun is today too?", everyone replies "Nun-nun!"
普通になんか私、やりそうな気がしちゃったそれ。
Actually, I feel like I'd normally do that.
やってみよう、やってみよう！
Let's try it, let's try it!
もう1回言って。
Say it one more time.
「ぬんは今日も？」「ぬんは今日も？」で、みんな「ぬんぬん」って。
You ask "Nun is today too?", and everyone replies "Nun-nun".
あ、オッケーオッケー。
Ah, okay, okay.
いくよー！
Here we go!
ぬんはー！今日もー！
Nun is! Today too!
ぬんぬん！
Nun-nun!
お、すごい！ペンライトもみんな青色で統一してくれてる！ありがとう！
Oh, amazing! Everyone's penlights are unified in blue! Thank you!
え、ねねちは？ねねちはどうする？
What about Nenechi? What about Nenechi?
ねねは今日もー、ねねは今日もー...
Nene is today too, Nene is today too...
なんだろう。え、これどこまでふざけていいんだろう？
What should it be? How far can I fool around?
いいんじゃない？100%ふざけよう、100%ふざけよう！
Isn't it fine? Let's goof off 100%, let's goof off 100%!
え、じゃ加「ねねは今日もー」って言ったら...
Then, when I say "Nene is today too"...
何て言ってほしいの？何て言ってほしいの？
What do you want them to say? What do you want them to say?
え、「うんぴっぴ」とかあり？
Is "Unpippi" okay?
それ、自分的にありなの？
Is that okay with you?
ありあり、いいじゃん！いいんだ。
Totally okay, why not! It's okay.
じゃあ海外のアニキ、everybody say 「うんぴっぴ」! Let's go! いくよ！
Then, overseas bros, everybody say "Unpippi"! Let's go! Here we go!
ねねは今日もー！
Nene is today too!
言ってくれたー！わー！最高！
They said it! Wow! Great!
最高、最高だよー！
Great, it's the best!
ねね、こんなにたくさんの人の前でこれ言うの恥ずかしい！
Nene feels so embarrassed saying this in front of so many people!
何言ってんの、めちゃくちゃ嬉しそうだったじゃん、今！やったー！みたいな。
What are you talking about? You looked so happy just now! Like, "Yay!"
あれもやろう、あれ！
Let's do that too, that!
ウェーブ！あ、ウェーブやろう！どっちから行く？どっちから行く？
The wave! Ah, let's do the wave! Which side do we start? Which side?
こっちから、こっちから。こっちからね！準備、スタンバイ！みんな！
From this side, from this side. From this side! Ready, stand by, everyone!
ウェーブ、やりましょう！ウェーブやるよー！
Let's do the wave! We're doing the wave!
いくよ。せーの！
Here we go. Ready, set!
戻ろう、戻ろう！戻るよ、戻るよー！
Let's bring it back, bring it back! Bringing it back, bringing it back!
早い、早い、早い！
Fast, fast, fast!
早い！戻って、戻って！まだついていけてない、みんな！
Too fast! Bring it back, bring it back! Everyone's not catching up yet!
戻って、戻ってー！
Bring it back, bring it back!
おおー！きたー！
Oooh! It's here!
完璧だ、みんな！ありがとう！
Perfect, everyone! Thank you!
みんな、でもここでね、あの、お知らせしなきゃいけないことがある。
Everyone, but we have something we must announce here.
そうなんだよね、ちょっとあるんだよね。えーって、もう言われてる。何も言ってないのに、もうって言われた。
That's right, there is a little something. They're already saying "Eh?". We haven't even said anything and they already said "Eh?".
みんな、察しが良いね。
Everyone is so quick to realize.
察しが良いね。
So quick to realize.
じゃあ、ぬん、ちょっと大事なお知らせ...あ、私なんだ！いいよ！
Then, Nun, please do the important announcement... Oh, it's me! Sure!
YouTube、TikTokでご覧の方は、ここまでになってしまいます！
For those watching on YouTube and TikTok, this is the end of the broadcast!
なんてことだー！
Oh my goodness!
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは、
If you want to keep having fun with us,
がい、がい、がい、概要欄から...
from the de, de, de, description section...
どこにあるかわかんないけど、概要欄からぜひ、配信サイトに来てください！
I don't know where it is, but please come to the streaming site from the description!
おいでー！
Come over!
というわけで、チラ見せはここまで！ここまで！
And so, that's it for the free preview! That's it!
せーの、Capture the Moment!
Ready, set, Capture the Moment!
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.